let savollar26 = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "advice",
        answer: "a. maslahat",
        options: [
            "a. maslahat",
            "b. ayblov",
            "c. ogohlantirish",
            "d. buyruq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "along",
        answer: "b. bo'ylab",
        options: [
            "a. orqali",
            "b. bo'ylab",
            "c. qarshi",
            "d. orqasida"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "attention",
        answer: "c. e'tibor",
        options: [
            "a. rozi bo'lish",
            "b. qiziqish",
            "c. e'tibor",
            "d. hurmat"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "to attract",
        answer: "a. jalb qilmoq",
        options: [
            "a. jalb qilmoq",
            "b. itarmoq",
            "c. e'tiborsiz qoldirmoq",
            "d. qo'yib yubormoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "to climb",
        answer: "d. tirmashib chiqmoq",
        options: [
            "a. yurmoq",
            "b. sakramoq",
            "c. yugurmoq",
            "d. tirmashib chiqmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "to drop",
        answer: "b. tomchilamoq",
        options: [
            "a. ko'tarmoq",
            "b. tomchilamoq",
            "c. ushlab turmoq",
            "d. tashlamoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "final",
        answer: "c. oxirgi",
        options: [
            "a. birinchi",
            "b. o'rta",
            "c. oxirgi",
            "d. oldingi"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "further",
        answer: "a. uzoqroq",
        options: [
            "a. uzoqroq",
            "b. yaqinroq",
            "c. oldinroq",
            "d. keyinroq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "to imply",
        answer: "d. nazarda tutmoq",
        options: [
            "a. tushuntirmoq",
            "b. aytyapti",
            "c. ko'rsatmoq",
            "d. nazarda tutmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "to maintain",
        answer: "b. saqlamoq",
        options: [
            "a. o'zgartirmoq",
            "b. saqlamoq",
            "c. buzmoq",
            "d. oldini olmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "neither",
        answer: "c. na",
        options: [
            "a. yoki",
            "b. ham",
            "c. na",
            "d. hamda"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: "otherwise",
        answer: "d. aks holda",
        options: [
            "a. lekin",
            "b. garchi",
            "c. shu sababli",
            "d. aks holda"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "physical",
        answer: "a. jismoniy",
        options: [
            "a. jismoniy",
            "b. ruhiy",
            "c. hissiy",
            "d. intelektual"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "to prove",
        answer: "b. isbotlamoq",
        options: [
            "a. taxmin qilmoq",
            "b. isbotlamoq",
            "c. da'vo qilmoq",
            "d. rad etmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "to react",
        answer: "a. munosabat bildirmoq",
        options: [
            "a. munosabat bildirmoq",
            "b. e'tiborsiz qoldirmoq",
            "c. ayblamoq",
            "d. o'zgartirmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 16,
        question: "to ride",
        answer: "d. minmoq",
        options: [
            "a. sakramoq",
            "b. suzmoq",
            "c. uchoq",
            "d. minmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 17,
        question: "situated",
        answer: "c. joylashgan",
        options: [
            "a. yo'qolgan",
            "b. uzoq",
            "c. joylashgan",
            "d. topilgan"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 18,
        question: "society",
        answer: "b. jamiyat",
        options: [
            "a. oila",
            "b. jamiyat",
            "c. do'stlar",
            "d. jamoa"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 19,
        question: "standard",
        answer: "d. me'zon",
        options: [
            "a. istisno",
            "b. o'rtacha",
            "c. chegara",
            "d. me'zon"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 20,
        question: "to suggest",
        answer: "a. taklif qilmoq",
        options: [
            "a. taklif qilmoq",
            "b. rad etmoq",
            "c. majburlamoq",
            "d. e'tiborsiz qoldirmoq"
        ]
    }
];
